No, no, no, no, no!
She could lose everything!
What are we gonna do?
It's your turn, Mistress.
Thank you so much for joining us.
Hey, I made the way All right.
Good morning, Nagumi.
Hey, good morning to you, Ronko.
Although feuds between Akihabara maids
have been relatively calm in recent years?
the incident last night is suspected to be
part of a long - That's Wuv Wuv Moonbeam.
Looks like you dudes really
smashed things up a bit.
Yes, we sure did.
Don't you think you went a little too far?
Do you think the chief is okay?
Nice shot!
Open up.
The plan was to make one of those
rodents kill one of your piglets.
It was needed in order to spark a dispute.
Wiping them out instead is unacceptable.
So you've created a huge problem for us.
Please stop.
Stay still.
Now don't move. Okay.
Four!
Nice shot!
If you value your pigsty of a life,
I suggest you pay me what you owe me.
Nice shot!
Sorry for the wait. Oink!
Right, here you go.
Would you like to order a drink first?
So it's business as usual?
Even after what happened?
For you, Master,
I recommend the first pigsty visit lunch
or the heartthrob ginger pork lunch.
But with the pigsty lunch,
you'll get to take a photo with a
couple of our cute little piglets.
I wonder if Yumechi does scary
stuff behind the scenes, too.
Here's the piggly jiggly rice
omelet you ordered master.
It comes with the ketchup doodle service
Now then, please allow me.
She shot people like it was nothing!
You look mad, pale, everything okay?
Uh, I just didn't sleep
very well last night.
Why don't you go for a stroll?
What do you mean by a stroll?
Well, the maid version of a stroll.
Welcome to the cafe!
Don't you want to come in?
Oinky-doink cafe.
Come to Oinky-doink cafe.
Come in, don't you?
Hold on.
Isn't this my chance
to run away from here?
Hey, pig face!
Think you could just hand those out on
our turf for your pathetic little store?
You might get yourself killed, meow.
Sorry, but I was told our group had
proper permission to hand these...
Maybe so, but you're at the
friggin' bottom of the heap, piggy.
That doesn't mean you can go
around being all cocky, Underly!
I'm very sorry!
Oinky-doink cafe!
Giving out flyers is
pretty tough, isn't it?
And most people are in such a hurry,
they don't even bother to take one!
That's true.
I'm definitely still learning.
Then you must be new to
the maid's stroll! I am.
Our place is tiny, though. That's okay.
Our cafe is pretty small as well. It is?
I should introduce myself.
I'm from Invader Café Destron.
My name is Nerula.
Oh, I'm Nagomi from Oinky Doink Café.
It's very nice to meet you.
We're not affiliated,
but as fellow maids, we
need to do the best we can,
even though the skirmishes
can be pretty rough at times.
Do the skirmishes and other scary stuff
happen a lot at the maid cafes? Hmm.
Well, of course, violence has
always been part of the deal.
But being a maid isn't all bad, you know?
You put your trust in your cafe and your
group, and they look after you in return.
The world of maid cafes is like a family.
Plus, you get to wear a cute uniform.
I guess you're right.
I think I'll keep at it
for a little longer then.
That's the spirit.
Think dream big go go, okay? I will.
Thank you, Nerula.
Hey, I'm back, you guys!
Oh, someone seems a lot happier. I am.
Time to dream pig.
True that.
Gotta dream pig. Go, go. Yeah.
Oh, hey there, Chief.
Sorry, girls.
This cafe is going out of business.
Huh?
Bronco, I need you to close
out and make it quick, please.
Yes, Chief.
Tell us what's going on, Chief.
No, you really don't
want to hear about it.
Tell us. All right.
Please say you'll lend us money.
How much money we talking?
A lot would be nice.
A lot, you say?
As much as I would like to lend you a
lot, I'd need some guaranteed collateral.
What kind of collateral?
Well, let me see.
Hmm, some land or a building?
Oh, how about our cafe? What?
That's too funny. You sold it?
You sold our cafe?
No, it's collateral!
Don't you know what that means?
You get it all back in the end.
Okay, manager, this is what we can offer.
This doesn't look like a lot.
Are you looking to get more?
It sure wouldn't hurt to
have a lot more. Oh, I see.
I know a wise way to invest that money.
You could even double it.
There's a members-only
club called Maid Casino.
You should try it.
No, thanks.
Do I look like a sucker to you?
If it involves maids, it's gotta be shady.
That's what everybody thinks right,
but it's actually totally
safe and legal and you can
increase your cash while
having fun It's a win-win.
I'll make money.
Of course you will a lot of
maids are regular customers
I can take you right away
if you'd like to try it out.
Maid casino wait you really went?
Calm down.
At least I'm still alive.
You should be dead.
Don't you realize how
precious this cafe is?
It's more important to a
maid than her own life.
You realize I did it for all of you.
You will never know what
it's like to have to
gamble for the sake of
everyone's well-being.
Wait, what?
What does that mean?
That's it?
This place is going to
shut down as easy as that?
We're so fucked.
We're done.
We're definitely screwed.
Hey, Chief, I'm done closing
out the register. Wait.
We're not done.
We've got the proceeds from
working our asses off right here.
You already spent the day
gambling, though, right?
With that little money?
No way.
If you assume that it's
impossible, it will be.
Self-doubt leads to failure.
Come on, now.
Let's say it together.
Say it.
Yes, we can.
We can if we try. Now let's go.
So what should we do right now?
You know the answer, right, Nagomi?
No, I don't.
My horoscope was totes-ma-goats today.
This'll be a cinch.
Gambling losses can only be
earned back with gambling.
This is where it all begins.
Our epic comeback.
Hit a jackpot straight to your heart.
Welcome to Maid Casino.
Yeah, yeah.
Hello, ladies.
Okay, where do you think we should start?
Take this.
Here.
Hmm.
Um as if i'd give you any
she lost all that money
and now she's back is she
an idiot so do you think?
We can bring more money
out of her no need to i
already got hold of her
maid cafe hey wait there?
Might be something else worth taking check
it out garbage we can turn into cash.
Hello, Mistress.
Is this your first time at our casino?
Yes, it is!
In that case, these slot machines
over here are great for beginners.
Thank you!
That's very kind of you!
Take your time, and please enjoy.
Mm-hmm.
I'm not sure how these
work, but I can dream pick.
Go, go!
Whoa, did I win?
Looks like you're doing good.
Hey, Chief.
It seems that way, huh?
So how is everybody else doing?
Come on, baby, come on.
Ooh, three potential bingos!
Looks like everyone's doing so well,
it's time to make our first move.
Oh, Lucky, I bet that's
enough for the cafe!
That's great, Chief, I'm so happy,
let's wrap it up here and get back home.
Are you sure you want to do that?
Gambling's no different
from how we experience life.
You can lose and can get
laughed at and ridiculed,
but what you can't do is run away!
But Chief, um...
You did good, Piglet.
I'll take it from here.
Boinky-doink!
At this rate, we should rake in enough
money to pay those Creatureland creeps!
You lost too, Ronco? Regretfully so.
We're completely out of money now.
Mistresses, are you enjoying yourselves?
I'm the dealer over at the
SuperDuper Poker Table,
and I'm here to let you know that
a new game is about to start.
Porker?
No, poker.
It's the game with the highest
stakes here at our casino.
Here's the minimum Baan.
There's no way we have enough.
Isn't there another way we can play?
Well, maybe.
Seeing as you're all
such hard-working maids,
I could suggest a way to play
without having enough chips.
A suggestion?
Like what?
Nothing drastic.
Just pledging your maid
futures as collateral.
Pledging our future? No!
No, I don't want to go! Please!
Hey, babe, you won't do anything!
Anything you want! Stop!
I don't want to go! No!
Don't! Don't take me!
The way it works is
you'll pledge the money
you're going to make in
the future as collateral,
so it's safe with zero risk.
Uh... We'll do it! Wait, what?
We can't do that! No way!
That's insane!
Isn't that right, Sheepon?
But we can't go home like this.
Huh?
The real deal starts now.
I knew it before we even started.
This way, mistresses.
I'll escort you to the poker area.
Let's go, ladies.
Much appreciated.
I'm starting to think that maybe everyone
at the oinky-doink is pretty messed up.
If you assume it's impossible, it will be.
Self-doubt only leads to
failure. Be confident.
So what do you think we should do?
You know the answer, Nagomi.
We should go home.
Poker is about reading the
other player's thoughts.
The key is how well
you can read them. Kay.
So your value as a maid translates
into the number of chips you have?
Wait a sec!
My lifetime income is pathetic!
I can't believe I have
less than Ronko or Nogomi!
And you have way too much over there!
Of course I do.
This mistress is making a move.
She's going all in.
It's a super duper chance! Yay!
Please, show your hand.
Ooh, the suspense! And open!
Three of a kind. Two
of a kind. Three, nine!
I thought I had a pretty
good shot with that
hand three nine can't
beat a five-five I guess?
Stupid piglet!
Whatever, that's one down if you have no
chips left to make your way over there?
Please.
What?
Damn.
Ah, shit.
Excuse me, is this the winning hand?
Mother.
What happens if we lose all the chips?
According to the rumors?
Up in the bitter cold of the Bering
Sea, You catch craps without rest.
Apparently, they wear you down until no
one would ever recognize you as a maid.
For real? Too funny.
So what are we going to do?
It's time for the next game to begin.
Then allow me to go first. Hey, Ronko.
What would you do if I asked you to
entrust me with all of your poker chips?
Then I would.
Both my chips and my life.
Thank you. That means a lot.
Looks like Yamichi's
gonna use Ronko's chips.
Then if she loses, that
means we're done for?
You've got this, piglet!
Come on!
The chief believes in you!
She's the last one, huh?
Alright, where should we ship off
those not-so-stellar pork butts?
First betting round is in play.
A raise.
With this move, this mistress here has
doubled the wager, increasing the pot.
It's a super duper big chance! Yay!
That customer's awfully
confident with her hand.
Makes me want to step up.
That should make things interesting.
What a dumb maid.
You have zero chances of winning.
She calls.
Check, please. Me too.
All right, it's the final betting round.
I'd like to raise.
That increases the wager eightfold.
It's the super duper last
and final chance. Yay!
Yumiichi, you've got this, I hope.
You know what you're doing, right?
No, no, no, no, no.
She could lose everything.
I hear the Bering Sea gets
down to minus 30 degrees.
They say if you fall in the
water, you die in three seconds.
No way.
There's no freaking way.
Well, dang it.
Yumiichi had today's best horoscope.
I thought for sure she'd win.
What are we gonna do?
It's your turn, mistress.
If you don't fold, it'll
be game over right now.
I'm all in.
I can't believe she went for it.
Is that wise to do?
Maybe she's all like, whatevs. Why?
There's no way she can win.
Why is she going for it with that hand?
Alright, please show your
hands in a clockwise direction.
Now, Mistress, please show us your hand.
You can't call yourself a maid
with that level of service.
Did you think I wouldn't
notice what you were doing?
During the game,
you never deal out the
top card to your associate
over there in order to
cheat your way to a win.
What?
The dealer's cheating?
That's not fair.
Not fair at all, hustler.
Better go back to your
hometown and start over, bitch.
You won some and lost some,
so we wouldn't ever catch on.
But when you're dealt a winning hand,
you have a bad habit of always
fiddling around with your glasses.
I see right through your tricks.
That confident bet was a bluff
to dupe me out of my winnings.
You didn't touch your glasses this time.
That means I have the
winning hand this round.
Mistress, what are you talking about?
Yumechi! Good one.
I knew you could do it.
Yeah, go!
A full house and a full house.
Did Yumechi just win the game?
No, she didn't. She lost. What?
Well, okay.
That was a good game, ladies.
Oh, wow, what a great game.
So very moving. Asshole.
Well, then, please come over this way.
Go ahead, go ahead.
All right, piggies, you'll
be departing at 2100.
I ain't going on no boat
to go crab catching.
My cafe, give me back my cafe.
You damn whining, pig turd.
You're going to delay our
shipment port for brains.
Time is money in this business.
You should have enough
sense to know that, right?
Think you crappy maids know better than
garbage can run a cafe here at Akiva,
of all places?
Maybe in like 50,000 years?
What the...
That's too funny.
We'll be taking back our cafe.
You lost wine, so get back in the cage!
Shut up, bitch.
You're the one who swindled us.
We're the ones struggling
and putting it hard.
Honest work.
This sucks!
Let's finish this shit.
Gosh, I haven't used a gun in ages.
There it is.
Hey, get back here, pigs!
I'll make you maids in hell with this!
Allow me to send you to hell.
There was an explosion last
night at a building in Akihabara.
According to investigators, it was due
to a skirmish in an underground casino.
This establishment had close
connections to a loan shark business.
So sad.
That's really awful stuff.
Apparently, it's not all
that unusual these days.
That explosion was a little too risky.
Ours from fireworks looks like
we're celebrating New Year's early.
But you know, the loan
sharks got in the cafe safe.
I think I did good, didn't I?
Uh, we're still behind on our dues.
I'm sure someone is going to come
by soon asking for it the soy sauce.
May I take it, please?
Sure.
I need to calm down at
least I'm still alive.
Today and tomorrow are all good.
We're all good at the house.
That's the truth of our life.
You're not stupid to be kidding me.
We're all good at the blood.
Thank you.
Thank you so
much
for
watching.